{
    "subject": "resource/Giovanni_Battista_Piranesi",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Artist",
    "human_readable": "Giovanni Battista Piranesi is an Artist.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9864957928657532,
            "question": "Is Giovanni Battista Piranesi considered a famous artist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9833431243896484,
            "question": "Was Giovanni Battista Piranesi a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.963922381401062,
            "question": "Can you name some artworks created by Giovanni Battista Piranesi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8364766836166382,
            "question": "How did Giovanni Battista Piranesi influence later artists?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7887670993804932,
            "question": "What profession was Giovanni Battista Piranesi known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7448039054870605,
            "question": "What is Giovanni Battista Piranesi most famous for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6428318619728088,
            "question": "What kind of works did Giovanni Battista Piranesi create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5737656950950623,
            "question": "What historical period is Giovanni Battista Piranesi associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5425025224685669,
            "question": "Are there any museums that feature works by Giovanni Battista Piranesi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5145683288574219,
            "question": "Where did Giovanni Battista Piranesi live and work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Giovanni Battista Piranesi is an Artist.",
            "html": "dbpedia_954_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any museums that feature works by Giovanni Battista Piranesi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_954_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What historical period is Giovanni Battista Piranesi associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_954_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of works did Giovanni Battista Piranesi create?",
            "html": "dbpedia_954_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_954_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_954_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_954_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_954_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_954_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_954_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_954_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_954_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_954_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_954_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided supports the triple that Giovanni Battista Piranesi is an artist. The documents mention him as a talented artist-engraver, master of etching, and printmaker famous for his etchings of Rome, among other things."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provided indicate that Giovanni Battista Piranesi was indeed an artist, specifically known for his etchings of Rome and fictitious prisons. Therefore, the statement \"Giovanni Battista Piranesi is an Artist\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}